A Guide to the Dept. of Employment Dispute Resolution Agency Head Correspondence and Subject Files, 1980-2012
Library of Virginia
- Agency head correspondence and subject files, 1980-2006.
  - Accession 43552, 1980-2006.
    - HB/SB30--Governor's Budget, 2000. (Box 15, Folder 23)
    - Hearing Info, March 16, 2001. (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Hearing Officer Meeting, 2001. (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - Hearing Officer Program, 2001. (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - Hearing Officers' Fees, 1997. (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Hearing Officers Handbook (original), 1998. (Box 28, Folder 18)
    - Hearing Officers--Legal Issues, 1995. (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Henderson: Access to Salary Data Information, 2000. (Box 7, Folder 47)
    - Higher Education Decentralization Pilot Programs--Status Report, 1994. (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - Hiring Exemption Form, n.d.. (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - HO Conference Materials 1999. (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Hobson, Harold, 1994. (Box 12, Folder 23)
    - Holland, Richard J., April 14, 1997. (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - House and Senate Documents Processing Guidelines, 1994. (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - HR Conference, November 29-December 1, 2000. (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - HR Conference Photos, October 1999. (Box 15a, Folder 1)
    - HR Leadership Conference Results, 1999. (Box 24, Folder 22)
    - HRO Labels, 2000. (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Hubbard, Clyde Follow-Up Meeting at JRCC, June 7, 2000. (Box 24, Folder 21)
    - Human Resources Generalist, 1995. (Box 18, Folder 51)
    - Human Resources Spring Conference, 1998. (Box 2, Folder 37)
    - Human Resources Spring Conference, 1998. (Box 2, Folder 38)
    - Hundley, Sheila; Ojumu, Afolabi; Morse, Roger; Ford, Henry; Wilson, Charles; Zottig, Renard, 1999. (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - IHRIS, 1995. (Box 18, Folder 52)
    - IHRIS Information--Integrated Human Resources Information Systems, 1998. (Box 15, Folder 13)
    - "I-J-K", 1994. (Box 28, Folder 21)
    - Imaging Technology Presentation DIT, May 19, 1999. (Box 15, Folder 14)
    - Incentive Based Voluntary Separation Program, 1995. (Box 18, Folder 12)
    - Incentive Pay Plan, 1990-1991. (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Inclement Weather Policy, 1987. (Box 28, Folder 22)
    - Insurance-Risk Management (DGS), 1998. (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - Intellectual Property Policy, 1985-1986. (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - Intellectual Property Policy/Grievance Procedures, 1986. (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Interagency Agreements--DPT--DERC (Discrimination), 1987. (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - Interagency Agreements--Human Rights--DPT--DERC (Discrimination), 2000. (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - Interagency Agreements--Human Rights and Rights of Disabled, 1998. (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - Interagency Placements, 1995. (Box 18, Folder 14)
    - Internet, 1996. (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Internet Privacy Guidelines Secretary of Technology, 2001. (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - Investigative Criteria, 1996. (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - Involuntary Resignation, 1987. (Box 12, Folder 16)
    - Involuntary Resignation, 1989. (Box 12, Folder 15)
    - Involuntary Separations--WTA, 1995. (Box 18, Folder 13)
    - IPMA, 1998. (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - ISDN Phones, March 1991. (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - IT Strategic Plan, 2001. (Box 22, Folder 21)
    - Jet Direct Card, 1999. (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - JLARC--Documents Produced, August 6, 1999. (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - JLARC--Documents Produced, October 1, 1999. (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - JLARC--Documents Produced, November 9, 1999. (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - JLARC--Documents Produced, November 10, 1999. (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - JLARC--Documents Provided, August 19, 1999. (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - JLARC--Documents Provided, October 13, 1999. (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - JLARC--Items Produced, August 16, 1999. (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - JLARC Study--Hearing Officers, 1999. (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - JLARC Study--Review of Use of Grievance Hearing Officers, 1999. (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - JLARC's Update to Review of the Use of Grievance Hearing Officers, May 25, 2001. (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - John Tyler Community College Information, April-October 1998. (Box 6, Folder 32)
    - Joint Commission on Management of the Commonwealth's Workforce, June 14, 1994. (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - Joint Commission on Management of the Commonwealth's Workforce, June 14, 1994. (Box 26, Folder 11)
    - Joint Commission on Management of the Commonwealth's Workforce, July 7, 1993. (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - Joint Commission on Management of the Commonwealth's Workforce, November 23, 1993. (Box 26, Folder 9)
    - JSRCC Training Schedule/Information, 1998. (Box 6, Folder 30)
    - June's Suggestions, 1997. (Box 28, Folder 9)
    - Just Cause Research, 1997. (Box 28, Folder 12)
    - Kaplan, Morris M., 1983. (Box 12, Folder 14)
    - Lag Pay, 1996. (Box 12, Folder 17)
    - LAN Maintenance Agreement, March 12, 1999-March 12, 2000. (Box 24, Folder 20)
    - Lassiter, Melissa, 2001. (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Law Library, 1990. (Box 12, Folder 18)
    - Lawrence, Bryon, 1999. (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Lease, May 1995. (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - Lease-One Capital Square, 1999. (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - Leave Sharing, 1996. (Box 18, Folder 19)
    - Leave Summary Reports, 1998. (Box 14, Folder 21)
    - Legal Issues, March 11, 1997. (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Legal Issues, 1997. (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Legal Issues Seminars, 1997. (Box 6, Folder 23)
    - Legal Issues Seminars, 1997. (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Legal Issues Seminars, August 12, 1997. (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Legal Issues--Video Taping, 1997. (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Legal Notices, 1994. (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Legislation, 2000. (Box 15, Folder 31)
    - Legislation (Farr's File), 2004. (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - Legislation (Main File), 2004. (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - Legislative Conference May 12, 2000, 2000. (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Legislative Conference--Richmond Marriott, May 12, 2000. (Box 20, Folder 13)
    - Legislative Information Services, 1991-1996. (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Legislative Materials--Legislative Submissions Materials, 2001. (Box 15, Folder 18)
    - Legislative Reporting Requirements, September 1999. (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Legislative Subscription Service, 2002. (Box 22, Folder 24)
    - Lexis-Nexis Information, 2002. (Box 22, Folder 18)
    - Lexis-Nexis On-Line Services, 1998. (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Liaison Officers Booklet, 1997. (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Link, Mary Ann, August 13, 1996. (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - List Server Information, 2003. (Box 24, Folder 12)
    - Lottery, 1997. (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - "M", 1997. (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Magazine Subscriptions/Newspaper Subscriptions, 1998. (Box 5, Folder 28)
    - Mailings, 1990. (Box 14, Folder 14)
    - Maps, July 1998. (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - Marketing Plan Consultant Agreement, 1996. (Box 2, Folder 34)
    - Marketing Plan Development, 1997. (Box 2, Folder 35)
    - Marketing Plan Quotes, 1996. (Box 2, Folder 36)
    - McCoy, Valerie, 2000. (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - MCVH--G.H., 1997. (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - Mediation Brochure, 1998. (Box 5, Folder 22)
    - Mediation Brochure Printing, 1996. (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - Mediation Evaluation Study--Contract # 962-97-3, 1997. (Box 29, Folder 30)
    - Mediation Info, 2000. (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Mediation (Neil's file), 1999. (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Mediation Program, 1999. (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - Mediation and Services Brochures, FY 1998. (Box 5, Folder 23)
    - Mediation Training Services RFP #905-13, 2001. (Box 14, Folder 15)
    - Meeting Rooms Usage, 1993. (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - Meeting with Toni--Information Financials Database Meeting, 2003. (Box 24, Folder 11)
    - Memberships, 1997. (Box 14, Folder 13)
    - Memo on Indebtedness, August 1996. (Box 18, Folder 54)
    - M.E.T.--Weekly Reports, 1998. (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - Ms. Mills; Mr. Waters, 1999. (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Mini CMI Conference--Williamsburg, December 3, 1998. (Box 20, Folder 23)
    - Minutes of Meetings (McPhie), December 1, 1998. (Box 20, Folder 25)
    - Miscellaneous Budget Materials, 2000. (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - Miscellaneous Paperwork (E. Williams, D. Price, 1999. (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Mitro, Maitreyee, 1998. (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Modem to Secretary's Office, 1992. (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - Morris, Douglas--Grievance Tapes, 1998. (Box 7, Folder 28)
    - MOU with Dept. of Information Technology--Upgrade of Server, 1998. (Box 1, Folder 31)
    - Move Information, 1999. (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Move Progress and Scheduing of 12th Floor Conference Room, 1999. (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - Moving File, 1999. (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - Moving and Relocation Regulations, 1990. (Box 14, Folder 16)
    - "N", 1993. (Box 14, Folder 17)
    - New Email Address, April 1998. (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Non-General Fund--Local Government 0200, 1995. (Box 18, Folder 57)
    - Non-General Fund--Mediation 0227, 1994. (Box 18, Folder 59)
    - Non-General Fund--POGL 0224, FY 1994-1995. (Box 18, Folder 58)
    - Oed. Rulings Enterprise, 1980-1986. (Box 12, Folder 26)
    - Office of the Attorney General #1, 1991. (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Office of the Attorney General #2, 1997. (Box 27, Folder 20)
    - Office of the Attorney General #3, 1998. (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Office of Comptroller, 1993-1997. (Box 27, Folder 8)
    - Office of the Comptroller's Directive 2-00--Financial Statement Preparation of State Agencies Directive, 2000. (Box 7, Folder 40)
    - Office of the Governor, 1998. (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - Office of Graphics Communications--DGS, 1997. (Box 5, Folder 20)
    - Office Signs, 1996. (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Oklahoma Merit Protection Commission Meeting, July 13, 2001. (Box 21, Folder 16)
    - Olsen, Ingrid, November 12, 1996. (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - O'Neill, Robert M., Dr., June 10, 1997. (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Open Door, 1994. (Box 18, Folder 33)
    - Open House Invitation List, n.d.. (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Organizational Charts, 1997. (Box 14, Folder 18)
    - Organizational Study of the Facilities Management Division, 1990. (Box 26, Folder 10)
    - Original Versions, 1995. (Box 28, Folder 14)
    - OSHA, 1997. (Box 18, Folder 32)
    - OSHA Logs, 1994. (Box 14, Folder 19)
    - Other Code Provisions re: Attorney's fees and comments, etc., 2004. (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - Outreach, 2000. (Box 7, Folder 52)
    - Outreach Info, 1998-1999. (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Overtime Approvals from DPT and Compensatory Time, 1995. (Box 18, Folder 17)
    - P-14, 2000. (Box 7, Folder 20)
    - P-14 Executive Secretary Application, 2000. (Box 20, Folder 30)
    - Parking Applications-DGS, 1999. (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - Parking-Exchange Place, 1997. (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - Part-time HO Directives-modified schedule, December 2000. (Box 7, Folder 39)
    - Patient Abuse Concerns, 1997. (Box 28, Folder 10)
    - Patient Abuse Information, n.d.. (Box 14, Folder 20)
    - Pay Increases (Lag Pay) Shifting of Pay Dates, 1996-1997. (Box 14, Folder 23)
    - Paychecks, 1985. (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Payroll Certification, 1996. (Box 14, Folder 22)
    - Payroll Information, 1998. (Box 14, Folder 25)
    - PC Software/Modem, 1994. (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - Performance Evaluation Form (Clerical), n.d.. (Box 29, Folder 16)
    - Performance Evaluation Form (Managerial), n.d.. (Box 29, Folder 14)
    - Performance Evaluation Forms, June 1983. (Box 29, Folder 13)
    - Performance Evaluation, Interim Executive, 1984. (Box 29, Folder 15)
    - Performance Evaluation Rulings and Summary, July 1989. (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - Performance Management Evaluation Implementation, 2001. (Box 22, Folder 28)
    - Performance Management--SAP, 2002. (Box 21, Folder 18)
    - Performance Measurements for Government--Arlington, Virginia, September 24-September 25, 2001. (Box 22, Folder 26)
    - Performance Measures, 1996. (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Performance Measures/Budget Documents, 2000-2002. (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Performance Measures--Pilot Project, 1995. (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - Performance Measures Updates, CY1999. (Box 15, Folder 27)
    - Performance Rating Distribution by EEO Code, June 1993. (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Personal Office's Workshop, 1995. (Box 18, Folder 60)
    - Personal Property Tax Relief, 1998. (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - Personnel Information, 1998. (Box 14, Folder 24)
    - Personnel Notes, November 1992. (Box 18, Folder 29)
    - Petway, Truman, 2001. (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Petway, Truman, 2001. (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Pilot Proposal--Dept. of Planning and Budget Performance Based Incentive Program, 1997. (Box 28, Folder 23)
    - Plan for Expenditure of Reappropriations, FY1999. (Box 15, Folder 26)
    - Plan for Expenditure--Reappropriation, FY2000. (Box 15, Folder 24)
    - Planning and Budget, 1999. (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Portable Overhead Projectors, 1993. (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Position Descriptions, 1998. (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Position Descriptions and Performance Standards--Official Copy, 1990. (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - Postage, 1994-1996. (Box 29, Folder 23)
    - Poster Order Information, 1997. (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - POW, January 1994. (Box 18, Folder 63)
    - POW, March 1994. (Box 18, Folder 62)
    - Press Inquiries--Warner Administration, 2003. (Box 24, Folder 18)
    - Press Releases, 1991. (Box 29, Folder 17)
    - Printer--to Mail, 1997. (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Printing, 1999. (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Printing, 1999. (Box 7, Folder 23)
    - Printing Specs Form, n.d.. (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - Printing Vendors, 1996. (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Privacy Protection, 1988. (Box 29, Folder 19)
    - Privacy Protection Act, June 11, 1996. (Box 6, Folder 18)
    - Privacy Protection Act and Freedom of Information Act, n.d.. (Box 18, Folder 21)
    - Privatization, 1997. (Box 29, Folder 21)
    - Privatization and Technology, April 6-8, 1997. (Box 29, Folder 22)
    - Probation Officers, 1985-1998. (Box 29, Folder 24)
    - Procurement Classes--Virginia Beach, November 18, 1998. (Box 20, Folder 28)
    - Procurement/Purchasing Information, 1998. (Box 5, Folder 30)
    - Projector Repair Project, 1997. (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Promotional Items, 1997. (Box 5, Folder 27)
    - ProScan Television, October 1995. (Box 6, Folder 28)
    - Public Debt News, 1997. (Box 5, Folder 41)
    - Public Relations, 1988. (Box 29, Folder 26)
    - Publication Policy, 2000. (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Purchase Orders, FY 1999. (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Quantum Tempories, 1999. (Box 20, Folder 26)
    - Quotes Received on 11 x 17 Gloss LOE cover, 2000 copies, one-sided, 1996. (Box 5, Folder 21)
    - "R", 1995-1998. (Box 29, Folder 27)
    - Reappropriations, FY1999. (Box 15, Folder 28)
    - Receipts--Conference Participants, 1997. (Box 2, Folder 39)
    - Receipts--Granite, 1998. (Box 5, Folder 26)
    - Recodification of 2.1 Exposure Draft, September 1999. (Box 21, Folder 10)
    - Recruit Modification, September 08, 2000. (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - Recruitment and Advertising Program, January 16, 2001. (Box 7, Folder 37)
    - Recycling Program, 1997. (Box 6, Folder 33)
    - Renovation Project, 1998. (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - Request to Attend Seminar (Doris), December 1998. (Box 20, Folder 27)
    - Request for Brochures, April 28, 2000. (Box 7, Folder 26)
    - Research on Receiving Evidence, 1997. (Box 28, Folder 11)
    - Responses to Requests for Information (Provided by DJH), 2001. (Box 7, Folder 35)
    - Return to Work Policy, September 21, 2001. (Box 22, Folder 23)
    - RFP Mediation, 1995-1998. (Box 29, Folder 28)
    - RFP Mediation 905-13, 2000. (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Right to Privacy, August 9, 1988. (Box 29, Folder 18)
    - Risk Assessment and Business Impact Analysis, March 20, 2000. (Box 7, Folder 53)
    - Round Table Meeting, May 7, 1996. (Box 12, Folder 21)
    - Round Table Meeting, July 26, 1996. (Box 12, Folder 20)
    - "S", 1997. (Box 12, Folder 27)
    - Salary Reference Data Information, 2000. (Box 22, Folder 27)
    - Savings Bond Campaign Meeting, 03/24/1999. (Box 5, Folder 40)
    - Savings Bond Drive, 1999. (Box 5, Folder 39)
    - SB 180 E, 1990. (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - SB 201, 2004. (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - SB 647 (Reynolds), 2003. (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - SB732--Dept. of Employee Relations Counselors: Grievance Procedure, 2000. (Box 15, Folder 20)
    - SCRRRAP, 1987. (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Second-Step Respondents, 1991. (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Secretary of Administration, July-December 1992. (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - Secretary of Administration, January-June 1993. (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - Secretary of Administration, January-June 1994. (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Secretary of Administration, July-December 1994. (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Secretary of Administration, 1996. (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Secretary of Administration, 1997. (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Secretary of Administration, 1998. (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - Secretary of Administration Draft Letters, 2000. (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Secretary of the Commonwealth, 1993. (Box 27, Folder 16)
    - Security, 1996. (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - Senator Schewel, 1991. (Box 12, Folder 28)
    - Sexual Harassment, 1990. (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Smith, Victoria, 2001. (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Smoking Policy, 1990. (Box 18, Folder 22)
    - SOA Weekly Reports, 1999. (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - SOA Weekly Reports, 2000. (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - SOA Weekly Reports, 2001. (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - SOA Weekly Reports, 2002. (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - SOA Weekly Reports, 2003. (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - SOA Weekly Reports, 2004. (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Social Security ID Number, 1990. (Box 18, Folder 26)
    - Social Service Case Scott County, 1987. (Box 6, Folder 24)
    - Social Services, Dept. of, 1993. (Box 12, Folder 24)
    - Sole Source Procurement, 1998. (Box 5, Folder 31)
    - Spring Hearing Officer Conference, 1998. (Box 28, Folder 17)
    - Staff Meeting 09/17/99, 1999. (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Staff Report (EDR), 2000. (Box 7, Folder 46)
    - Staff Retreat, the Virginia Diocesan Center at Roslyn, August 11, 2000. (Box 24, Folder 24)
    - Standard Operating Procedure, 2000. (Box 24, Folder 25)
    - Standards of Conduct, 1989. (Box 12, Folder 29)
    - State Agency Meeting Rooms, 1994. (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - State Car Rental Rates, 2001. (Box 21, Folder 21)
    - State Fair of Virginia, 1994. (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - State Government Organization, 1995. (Box 18, Folder 30)
    - State Mail System, 1994. (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - State Police, Dept. of, 1997. (Box 12, Folder 30)
    - State Records Center Information, 1998. (Box 24, Folder 32)
    - State Vehicle Reservations, 1996. (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - Statewide Strategic Planning Input--DERC's Response to DPB, October 8, 1998. (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Strategic Plan, 2001. (Box 21, Folder 15)
    - Strategic Plan, 2003. (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Strategic Plan, 2004. (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Strategic Plan: Dept. of Employee Relations Counselors, July 1999-April 2000. (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Strategic Plan--Focus Agenda, 2000. (Box 20, Folder 20)
    - Strategic Plan Materials, 1999. (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Strategic Planning Meeting, January 14, 2004. (Box 20, Folder 35)
    - Strategic Plans, 1999-2001. (Box 22, Folder 20)
    - Substitute W-9, 1998. (Box 5, Folder 32)
    - Suggestions from the Committee, 1997. (Box 28, Folder 8)
    - Summary of Recent Employee Law Case Decisions, June7, 1996. (Box 23, Folder 10)
    - Summary of Recent Federal and State Cases Involving Employment and Labor Law Issues, 1998. (Box 27, Folder 19)
    - Summary of U. S. Supreme Court Cases, October 1994-July 1995. (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - Summer Labor and Employment Law Course, 1999. (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - Supreme Court of Virginia, 1997. (Box 6, Folder 25)
    - Surplus Items, April 2000. (Box 24, Folder 19)
    - Surplus PCs (check out), 1996. (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - SWOT Analysis, February 23, 2004. (Box 24, Folder 13)
    - "T", 1995. (Box 6, Folder 26)
    - Talent Bank User Survey, 1994. (Box 18, Folder 48)
    - Tape Recording and Privacy from Statutory Standpoint, September 1997. (Box 29, Folder 20)
    - Tax Exempt Forms (blank), n.d.. (Box 5, Folder 43)
    - Tax Exempt Forms Filed w/ Vendors, 2005. (Box 5, Folder 42)
    - TCO, October 2001. (Box 24, Folder 14)
    - Telecast, May 1995. (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Telecommunications Device for the Deaf, 1989. (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - Telecommuting Information, 2003. (Box 20, Folder 34)
    - Telecommuting Information, 2003. (Box 24, Folder 9)
    - Telecommuting Provisions, 2003. (Box 24, Folder 10)
    - Teleconferencing, 1994. (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - Telephone Credit Cards, 2000. (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Telephone Instructions, 1989. (Box 5, Folder 47)
    - Telephone/Line Project, 1998. (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Telephone Move Information, 1999. (Box 7, Folder 29)
    - Telephone Service Request, 1997. (Box 1, Folder 32)
    - Third-Step Management Levels, 1991. (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Thomas, Jan, Dr., May 13, 1997. (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - Tips for Conducting Sexual Harassment Investigations, September 10, 1996. (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - Tips for a Successful Hearing Brochure, May 1998. (Box 5, Folder 24)
    - Training Information--EDR, 2001. (Box 7, Folder 30)
    - Training Packets Progress, 1999. (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Training--UVA, 1995-1996. (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - Transportation, 1998. (Box 5, Folder 48)
    - Transportation, 1998. (Box 6, Folder 27)
    - Travel Regulations, 1992. (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - Two Year Budget, 1998-2000. (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - "U", 1993-1994. (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - Ukrop's Charge Card, 2001. (Box 1, Folder 35)
    - Ukrop's Receipts, 1998. (Box 1, Folder 36)
    - Unemployment Benefits and WTA, 1995. (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - Unemployment Insurance Information, 1998. (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - Union, 1992. (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - United State District Court, 1999. (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - University of Richmond--Clinical, 1996. (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - Updated POs, 1998. (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - UPS Ground Account-DGS, 1995. (Box 2, Folder 30)
    - UPS Next Day Air, 1997. (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - UVA Capitol Club--Professor Del Conte, September 17, 2001. (Box 21, Folder 20)
    - "V", 1998. (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - VBA Outline, 2000. (Box 20, Folder 11)
    - VBO Bulletin Board, 1998. (Box 5, Folder 36)
    - VCE Request Release Forms, 1997. (Box 5, Folder 52)
    - VCE Waiver Forms, 1998. (Box 5, Folder 53)
    - VCU--Panel of Inquiry Investigative Report, October 1988. (Box 25, Folder 7)
    - VCR Police Report, 1994. (Box 1, Folder 37)
    - VDOT VFM Rental Rates, 2000. (Box 7, Folder 45)
    - VEI Nominations, 2000. (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - VEI--Virginia Beach (Atkinson) (Non-Smoking Room), October 15-October 20, 2000. (Box 15, Folder 32)
    - Vending Machine, 1998. (Box 5, Folder 49)
    - Veterans Administration, n.d.. (Box 25, Folder 9)
    - Video, 1995. (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - Videoconferencing Information, 2002. (Box 22, Folder 19)
    - Videotape, 1995. (Box 18, Folder 67)
    - Videotape, 1995. (Box 18, Folder 68)
    - VIP Net Information--EDR Website, 2004. (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - Virginia Commonwealth University, 1998. (Box 25, Folder 8)
    - Virginia Correctional Enterprise, 1999. (Box 5, Folder 51)
    - Virginia Council on Human Rights--Results of Benchmark Survey, June 1998. (Box 21, Folder 19)
    - Virginia Credit Union, 1998. (Box 1, Folder 38)
    - Virginia Employment Commission, 1996. (Box 25, Folder 10)
    - Virginia Executive Institute, 1993. (Box 25, Folder 11)
    - Virginia Executive Institute Conference, August 1998. (Box 24, Folder 31)
    - Virginia Income Tax Withholding Form and ID, 1999. (Box 5, Folder 45)
    - Virginia Industry for the Blind, 1996. (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - Virginia Mediation Network, 2001. (Box 22, Folder 29)
    - Virginia Museum of Fine Arts (Personnel Reorganization), 1992. (Box 25, Folder 17)